Please contact us for any inquiries
turkision@gmail.com
We are going to İnegöl.
It's about time, Osman Bey.
My bey!
My bey, someone is coming!
Alps, wait!
We saved you from the vizier...
thanks to Kosses.
Welcome, Michael Kosses.
Thank you, Osman Bey.
Allah damn it!
What happened here?
Osman.
They ran away.
What is this, Konur Alp?
Couldn't you stop a few men?
They played us.
We tried to stop them but---
But you couldn't stop them even
though you sensed it.
Maybe I overvalue you.
One of the dervishes gave
sherbet to the guards.
When they fell a sleep,
they entered.
But this won't happen again,
my vizier.
A dervish?
I was right.
Edebali...
you are helping Osman, huh?
You are here in time, Celali.
He'll understand what happens
when he works with Osman.
He'll pay for it.
As you order, my vizier.
Pull yourself together.
You'll find Osman.
I won't accept any other mistake.
As you order, my vizier.
We swore a sacred oath to
stand together with the lords.
But this betrayal of
dishonorable Nikola...
overrides my oath.
The desire for vengeance
made you work with us, Kosses.
It is.
Osman Bey.
But don't forget.
It's only until we deal with Nikola.
If you say so.
Alright.
But don't you work behind
my back...
under the disguise of vengeance.
Don't worry.
I'll only play with those
who hurt me.
Be at ease.
I always am.
Both on games...
and traps.
Don't worry.
But...
I say that...
it's my people's good that will
be on the markets.
And there are your goods.
I don't want them to get
harmed.
This market in İnegöl...
isn't good for you or me.
We'll destroy that market.
I understand.
So, what do you want from me?
Your goods are going there too.
The cart that will take them...
will carry the alps and the
oil that will burn the market down.
We'll burn them down.
A lord incapable of protecting
his own lands...
can't own such a market.
And then?
When the vizier has no choice, he'll
set the market in Harmankaya.
You thought well.
But neither the vizier nor the Nikola
would ever want that.
The market won't be in Harmankaya...
but in a better place,
Bilecik.
And I'll tell them about the benefits
of having the market in Bilecik.
And Rogatus? Will you
be able to control him?
To revenge from Nikola...
I can even convince the devil.
Alright.
The market will be in Bilecik.
You'll confront the vizier.
And I'll finish off that dishonorable
Nikola...
who tried to kill my Mari.
We all will get what we want.
Mari is with us.
You returned from your mistake.
Mari.
We should get your brother's approval.
With Allah's order...
and our holy prophet's words...
we ask for your
sister Maria...
for my brother Turgut.
With one condition
The wedding will be at Harmankaya.
Alright.
Let it be Harmankaya.
Then, I allow my sister Mari...
to marry Turgut Bey.
Thank you.
Mari.
Brother.
My dear.
I always wanted the best for you.
After the market burns...
you can't stay here. All eyes
will be on you.
So, I'll host you at Harmankaya.
Let's take care of this İnegöl
issue first.
My friend Zehra.
One of the tribeswomen.
Sheik Edebalı!
While we were here...
Osman avoided my soldiers, took his alps
and left.
Are you aware of that?
My soldiers passed out because
of a sherbet...
given by ahis.
You did an unjust thing.
Without a proof...
you threw the alps
to the dungeon.
Osman Bey...
was assuring justice...
and I stood by him.
And I always will.
You will regret that, Edebalı.
You will pay dearly for it.
If the price is...
our lives leaving our bodies...
don't hold back.
What you see as a punishment
is an award for us.
What you see as an award
is a punishment for us.
Arrest the rebellious sheik!
-Leave the sheik!
-Leave him! My Sheik!
Let our sheik go!
Bala Hatun!
-Bala!
-Why are you taking my father?
What will you do to him?
Don't worry.
I'll leave your father
to a professional.
-Let him go!
-My sweetheart.
My sweetheart, stop.
Whatever comes from our Allah...
is a gift.
Wait.
Be patient.
Take him!
No! No, father!
Let my father go!
Father! Let him go!
My sheik!
Father...
Oh, my lion son.
All the troubles we have...
is endured because I have
you in my heart.
Your shining eyes...
I live to let them see further
from these lands.
My Orhan.
Mashallah.
He'll be as valiant as
his father, inshallah.
He will.
He will, Malhun.
You look kindly at Orhan.
Look how they love him.
Both their eyes are shining.
Orhan is very lucky.
So will be our child.
After I have a child...
I'll look at my child in a way
that my eyes will shine like stars.
Just as it shines when
I look at you.
I hope so, Turgut.
My bey.
Take him.
Baysungur.
My bey, Vizier Alemşah!
He arrested Sheik Edebalı...
and threw him to the dungeon.
They are attacking...
and now the dungeon!
My sheik!
My bey, allow me to go and
accompany my sheik.
-Allow me, my bey.
-Kumral Abdal!
Wait.
My bey, allow me to cut their throats!
Cerkutay, wait.
My bey, allow me to
take his head!
Allow me, my bey!
Alps! Wait!
Wait!
The one who does that
to ulema...
is the greatest traitor.
The vizier wants us to do that.
He wants us to enter the
dungeon and take our sheik.
But...
we won't do that.
we'll lead the folk to a revolt.
Turgut Bey.
Go to Söğüt.
All the people are loyal to my sheik.
Tell them that they shouldn't stop
until the tyrant's cruelty ends.
It's your duty.
Alright, Osman Bey.
-Malhun.
-My bey.
Go to the tribe.
Keep your eyes on my brother.
As you order, my bey.
Alps!
It's time to cut down the
tyrant!
We are going to İnegöl.
As you order, my bey.
No... No! No!
Not this.
Take this off. I want to take
the best to the market.
Oh, my dear friend Kosses!
Welcome!
Julia, allow us.
As you want, Lord Rogatus.
You too.
We have a problem.
What is it?
Nikola and the vizier.
They have secret agreements.
Why didn't I think this before?
They are old friends.
That's why.
What's why?
That's why Nikola wants to be with
the vizier and take us out.
Understand it, Rogatus.
Even his share is twice of ours.
And tell me.
Why is the market in İnegöl?
Remember how he talked when we
objected to Nikola.
They are using us, Rogatus.
He'll strengthen Nikola economically
by using us.
Then, the stronger Nikola will unite with
the Vizier and destroy us.
Look at this.
I understand.
By taking twice the share,
they'll remove us from the market.
I talked to a merchant.
Rogatus.
Nikola ordered a great amount
of swords and shields.
And he is recruiting soldiers
from the villages.
Think about it.
He already ordered some before
even getting his share.
And, Rogatus.
Do you think Vizier Alemşah...
would allow Nikola to
attack the Turks?
Speak more clearly, Kosses.
Speak more clearly!!
Let me be clear.
Lord Rogatus.
Those swords...
if they can't spill Turkish blood...
whose blood will they spill?
What do you offer to do?
I don't know.
The balance can change at any moment
in these lands.
But of course, we'll get a chance.
Of course, we will.
Allah.
Allah. Allah.
I remembered the great imam, Akça.
That holy person suffered so much
for speaking the truth.
Ulema has never bowed
against the tyrants.
And we'll walk on the path
we know to be righteous.
We won't turn our back to
the turth...
because of fearing the
tyrant vizier.
Thank Allah, my sheik.
We can stand against the tyrant.
Now, start speaking, sheik.
Where is Osman?
Don't touch my sheik!
Or you'll have a broken hand!
Hit me! Don't touch my sheik.
Until you tell me where
Osman is...
I'll rip your skin
off your bones.
Go ahead.
Speak to the people.
As you order, my bey.
Come on.
Salam Alaikum.
Alaikum Salam.
It's Osman Bey's order.
Tomorrow, no one will open
their shops.
They'll stop the production.
-Alright.
Vizier Alemşah put our
vizier in the dungeon.
We can't leave our sheik
in the dungeon! We must do something.
They put our sheik in the dungeon!
How could they?
How can they do that?
How can they put our sheik
in the dungeon? Traitors!
Is this just?
How can this happen?
Traitors!
This can't happen!
You can't put Sheik Edebali
on the dungeon!
You can't do this!
I think you should speak, sheik.
It's your turn now.
Instead of speaking to a tyrant...
I rather spend all my
life in this dungeon.
We gave you more than enough time,
sheik!
What are you doing?
How can you hit Sheik Edebali?
It's Vizier Alemşah's order.
If he doesn't speak...
I'm allowed to do what's
needed.
Then, you'll wait, Celali!
Sheik Edebali will speak
when he wants to.
And you will wait.
But you won't hit him.
Sheik Edebali is a friend to Allah.
The hand you raise against him can
fall any moment.
Now, leave!
Soldier, give me the keys.
Sheik Edebali, are you alright?
What are you doing...
under Yezid's command, son?
Rogatus is confused enough, Osman Bey.
After we burn their market in İnegöl,
he'll be convinced.
Let's enter İnegöl with
your carts...
and burn the market.
After flames rise...
Rogatus will be convinced.
After burning it, we can fight
our way out, my bey.
Yes. Those who survive do survive.
Those who don't will be martyrs.
Right, brothers?
We missed fighting, my bey.
We are itching, my bey.
May Allah bless our jihad, my bey.
Mashallah.
If I hadn't seen it with my eyes,
heard it with my ears...
I wouldn't believe it, Osman Bey.
You are lucky to have
such brave soldiers.
This is what you are missing.
They aren't soldiers.
They brothers and comrades
to one other...
their hearts are filled
with faith...
they are Kayı alps!
Alright.
Then, I'll do everything I can to
take this small...
but brave army out of İnegöl alive.
I know the way.
You thought well, Kosses.
You thought well.
Alps.
You'll be cautious.
You'll check everywhere.
But no one will get hurt.
You'll memorize the walls, houses,
towers and even the ground.
They'll help us during our conquest.
As you order, my bey.
-Alright, my bey.
-Alright.
We started the jihad as
soon as we came, Osman Bey.
Mashallah to my valiant.
Come on, alps.
İnegöl Castle
These are all examples.
This iron is from Harmankaya.
Our gems are from Bilecik.
And the leathers will be from İnegöl.
And this...
as the symbol of the capable
smiths of the Turks...
from Söğüt.
You thought well, Nikola.
But our smiths don't forge with
anything but our own iron.
Gündüz Bey.
We are in a new order now.
When the capable smiths of the Turks
realize how much they can profit...
they'll change their minds.
Alright.
With these materials,
we'll make the strongest...
sharpest, best swords
of the world!
But is it enough?
It isn't!
At the same time, we'll make the
best sheaths.
It seems like you lived for this moment.
You were so enthusiastic.
Let's not say I lived
for this moment but...
let's say I waited for Vizier Alemşah.
We owe it all to him.
Vizier Alemşah.
I'm grateful that you showed us
how strong we are together.
Once we hold that sheath together,
Nikola...
then, we'll be even stronger.
Osman took his alps from the dungeon.
He took his alps but soon his alps will
be without a bey.
Osman entered a road that he
can't return.
He'll pay dearly.
You know the importance of this market
as much as I do, Nikola.
But I don't want any weakness.
That's on me.
Even a fly can't fly without
getting noticed by me.
But, Vizier Alemşah...
I have a little question.
I wanted to kill Mari.
So...
Turgut took her from me.
Nikola.
Does Kosses know that?
We'll see...
if he loses to his anger when
he comes here...
he might hurt our
mutual interests.
Vizier Alemşah, are you with me?
Take care of the market now.
We'll talk.
Where is my dear friend Kosses?
We did our part.
The rest is on the people
of Söğüt.
Don't worry, Turgut Bey.
The people won't return before
saving our sheik.
-In peace.
-Thank you:
To the forest, alps!
Soldiers! Bring the horses.
I apologize, my friends.
I'm late.
I hope I didn't miss anything important.
Welcome, Kosses.
You didn't miss much.
The Vizier and Nikola took care of all.
They didn't leave anything to us!
-Right, Nikola?
-Yes.
After all, you are my guests.
We are grateful, Nikola.
Come on.
Alps.
So... where is Mari?
Why are you alone?
Mari has gone to make preparations
of our wedding.
She is in Constantinie.
You sent her alone while
our enemies are following us.
I'll break your head if something
happens to her, my friend.
How low you are!
Nicola.
You lie to me in the face!
You have a short time left.
How are you, Gündüz Bey?
Thank you, Lord Kosses.
I heard that Osman got his Alps back.
Does that fear you?
Osman disobeys.
But I am not afraid of my brother.
Of course.
Let's eat!
It's time to eat.
Let's go into the castle.
Soldier!
What is this?
What's happening?
Osman!
This is Osman's job!
Because of you!
You did it!
It's because of you!
You let Osman in!
Watch your mouth, Nikola!
I am here for the wealth of my people!
Why would I harm the market?
Why did I trust a Kayi?
I should have never trusted a Turk!
Never!
Nikola, watch your words!
Don't put the blame on Gündüz Bey
because of your carelessness!
I vouch for his loyalty!
Here is the opportunity.
We need to turn the tables on us.
Tell them to set the market in Bilecik.
We have to break Nikola's power.
Do you see what your brother did,
Gündüz Bey?
It can't be Osman!
I can't believe it!
Why would he want to harm his own people?
Who else could it be other than Osman,
Gündüz Bey?
He wants to ruin the market and
damage our honor.
He doesn't see what's good for his people.
What I want from you to tell your people
about what Osman has done here!
Osman is a rebel who doesn't care
about the wealth of his people!
My Bey, go.
We'll handle.
All for one, one for all, Kutan.
Where are you going, Turgut Bey?
Come on now.
I have been waiting for this moment.
Hay Masha Allah (praise be)
Your breath shall burst, my valiant.
Thank you, Kumral Abdal.
Masha Allah. (praise be!)
You have a gifted occupation.
Don't take me wrong, but are you
talking about shepherding?
Yes, Mari Hatun.
Shepherding is sacred.
Our prophet Hadrat Mohammed was a
shepherd too.
Not only our prophet...
Not only him...
But also Abel, son of Hadrat Adam.
Prophet Moses, Prophet David.
They were shepherds too.
Right.
Muhammed, whose name and self is beautiful
said...
...''Allah did not send any prophet who
was not a shepherd.''
The companions asked,
"You too, the Prophet of Allah?"
He said ''Yes...
...once I was a shepherd in Mekka.''
Why is shepherding so important?
Shepherding means patience.
You wake up at the first light
of the day...
...and herd many animals.
You protect them.
Only with patience, you can bear this.
Waiting takes patience, Mari Hatun.
Alps!
Retreat!
Come on!
See how the counters were burning?
We warmed İnegöl up!
The bazaar was in flames.
Long live, Osman Bey!
Stop! Nikola's soldiers are everywhere.
Mashallah to my valiants!
Mashallah!
Where are we going now, my Bey?
Kosses have shown us he is a friend.
Now, the most secure place is Harmankaya.
We are going to Harmankaya.
-Cerkutay.
-My Bey.
Inform Turgut Bey.
Tell him to take Mari and come.
Since we are going to Harmankaya...
...let's have a wedding tonight!
As you order, my Bey.
Alps!
Back to the horses.
Guests need food.
Don't.
You are the guest.
Kumral Abdal.
Can you tell me about your Prophet?
I wondered much more after
getting to know you.
Turgut!
You are hurt!
Are you fine?
I am well, it is nothing important.
O, the healer.
We must take measure.
Come, sit here.
Kumral Abdal!
Don't be afraid, Mari Hatun.
It is not deep.
We will apply ointment and bandage it.
He will be fine.
I am fine, Mari.
Don't worry.
Does it hurt much?
Does the place you touch ever hurt?
Your hands are healing for me.
Now...
...the roads are dangerous.
There are Vizier's men everywhere.
They came after me while
I was coming here.
I got rid of them but soon they'll be here
Kumral Abdal.
I will check outside.
Put the ointment.
Thank you.
Mari.
Now that we are getting married...
... and you are Christian.
I am Muslim.
Have you ever thought of...
...becoming a Muslim?
Is there such a rule to get married?
No, there is no pressure in our religion.
But when I heard you asking about
our Prophet.
No, I love my religion.
Good.
Can we come in?
Come in.
I brought news from Osman Bey,
Turgut Bey.
My Bey told me to tell you...
...to take Mari and...
...come to Harmankaya.
We are having a wedding!
Our wedding is close too.
You are very lucky. I've been waiting
for so long.
I couldn't convince Aygül Hatun.
You are really fast.
I hope you get as you wish, Cerkutay.
-Thank you.
-Thank you, Cerkutay.
Thank you.
Why do you look sad?
Don't you want to get married?
No, I want to. I want it so much.
But I am afraid, Turgut.
What if something happens again?
Don't worry, also, we got used to it.
Even if your brother Kosses breaks his
word, I will take you out of Harmankaya.
I'll burn there too, for you.
But know that no one can take you from me.
No one.
Are you ready Mari Hatun?
The wedding awaits!
İnegöl Castle
How could you let this disgrace, Nikola?
I didn't let anything!
I took all the measures!
But Osman...
Osman is running around your castle with
his three alps.
What do you do?
You are right, Vizier Alemşah.
Why are these three alps are out?
Looks like you failed too.
Stop with the excuses, Nikola.
The disgrace outside is your doing.
And we need to find a solution to it right
now.
What solution Kosses?
That bazaar will open!
No, no, no.
We can't fall into the same hole.
Obviously, you can't protect your castle
as you should.
We can't trust İnegöl with such a big
bazaar.
Rogatus...
...you make no sense.
What do you suggest?
Bilecik.
I would never let such a thing happen.
Bilecik is the most suitable spot for
the bazaar.
Even the place of bazaar is ready.
I agree.
The same mistake won't happen again.
The best is Bilecik.
I trust you Rogatus.
The discussion is over.
Why didn't you tell me Osman was coming
to the Söğüt?
So that you could give Osman Bey to that
Vizier?
Hear yourself, Malhun Hatun.
You recognized me as someone bad.
But let me tell you...
...my only goal is to acquit my brother.
If he comes and surrenders now...
... I will go to Konya with him.
But as Osman continues to rebel
like this...
...things will get all complicated.
He ruined İnegöl.
Good for him.
Allah bless his hands.
What are you saying, mother?
Mother.
Osman isn't thinking about anyone.
Because he burnt İnegöl, the Lords came
over me.
They were going to kill me there
if it weren't for Vizier Alemşah.
My life isn't important, mother.
I would sacrifice myself.
What's important is our tribe.
The welfare of our tribe.
You all know very well what will happen
to the tribe...
...if the commerce is over.
Osman must stop.
Otherwise, what he's done will be a big
trouble for him.
There is no day without trouble
for a valiant, Gündüz Bey.
That Vizier you love, support...
...put my father in a dungeon!
What are you talking about, Bala Hatun?
What is Sheik Edebalı doing in a dungeon?
Ask that to your friend Vizier.
I pity you for trusting that Vizier...
...and not your brother.
That Vizier arrested my father
and took him away.
Blacksmith Davud encouraged the people.
People rebelled but, there is no use.
The Vizier achieved his purpose.
My father is now in a dungeon, Gündüz Bey!
If you are strong enough, then first,
get our Sheik out of the dungeon.
Bala Hatun.
I will talk to the Vizier.
Don't worry.
I won't leave my Sheik Edebalı in
that dungeon.
When, Gündüz Bey?
The Vizier is now in İnegöl.
I know he is there.
If he were in Söğüt, I would go to him
now.
But I will, the first thing
in the morning.
If my name is Gündüz Bey...
...I will take Sheik Edebalı.
Julia, you go and get the carriages ready.
As you wish, Rogatus.
Thank you for trusting me, my friend.
This way, we'll get the bigger share.
Of course, you will get the biggest
as the bazaar will be in Bilecik.
But the Vizier is deadly mad at Nikola.
Because his mistake nullified
all the moves of the Vizier.
Now we must strike the fatal hit.
You have to help me.
I will take Nikola for what he's done
to Mari...
...when they enter Bilecik.
I hope that is all right for you.
I just didn't like you involving me
in this.
But the gain you have given me
is priceless.
Also, this Osman.
I want you to take him in when Osman
comes to Bilecik.
What?
He will face the Vizier.
Osman? Are you out of your mind?
In my castle?
You are forgetting, Rogatus.
Enemy of our enemy is our friend.
I can't believe you sometimes, Kosses.
It amazes me what you can do
for your goals.
Don't, please. You saw the risk too.
If we do not act together with Osman,
they will unite and destroy us.
But now, Osman will take the Vizier.
I will take Nikola.
And you will take the gold from the trade.
Isn't it nice?
Let's hope so.
We don't hope.
We make it happen.
Harmankaya Castle
You look gorgeous, my lady.
Thank you Aygül.
This really is a great dress.
Mari...
...what's beautiful isn't the dress...
...it is the one inside it.
Come on.
We don't leave the bride without henna.
May Allah make you happy.
Thank you.
Can I come in?
Come in.
Mari.
You look so beautiful.
So beautiful.
Turgut Bey.
Come on.
Come on. Let's not make them wait.
Vizier, Edebalı is not speaking.
He is very secretive.
But I don't think he knows where
Osman is.
If even you couldn't make him talk...
...he must not know.
Actually, if I could whip him,
he would talk...
... even if he didn't know, but...
...Konuralp came and stopped me.
-Can I come in, my Vizier?
-Come in.
My Vizier...
...Sheik Edebalı is not important only for
Kayı and Söğüt...
...all the Oghuz people respect him.
Torturing him will only lower us.
A traitor is a traitor.
What lowers us is not punishing a traitor.
Konuralp is right, Celali.
We should treat Edebalı fairly...
...even if he is in a dungeon.
We shouldn't distance him from ourselves.
We need Edebalı for our purposes.
You go to Kayı tribe, Celali.
Watch closely. There must be
someone going to Osman.
As you order, my Vizier.
Harmankaya Castle
I bear witness that there is no god
but Allah, and I bear witness that...
...Muhammad (PBUH) is the servant
and Messenger of Allah.
Daughter of Baltu, Mari, do you take son
of Doğan Bey, Turgut...
...as your husband for two hundred
dirhams of gold...
...and thirty sheep?
I do.
Do you?
Son of Doğan Bey, Turgut...
...do you take daughter of Baltu, Mari
as your wife...
...and confirm your mehr?
I do.
-Do you?
-I do.
Do you testify?
We do.
May Allah bless your marriage.
Amen.
O Allah...
...we witnessed the marriage of
these two people.
You witness too.
Amen.
May Allah bless your marriage.
Grant love...
...livelihood and perseverance to
this couple's marriage.
Amen.
Don't give them lovelessness, discord
and separation.
Amen!
Al-fatehah!
Look...
...Turgut Bey and Mari met after us.
But they are getting married before us.
When will we get married?
Come on, you crazy!
Now that the wedding is done...
...it's time to draw our swords.
Congratulations, Osman Bey.
A superb wedding in such a short time!
Unbelievable.
Don't be surprised, Kosses.
We are always ready for war and weddings.
I see.
By the way, I have good news.
Rogatus is convinced.
He'll take you in the Bilecik Castle.
Vizier Alam Shah!
I'll hunt you down.
And I am going to take revenge from
that dishonest Nikola...
...who tried to kill Mari.
Good luck.
Your breed shall continue.
You have always stood with me.
Thank you Osman Bey.
Thank you.
Mari.
I want you to be happy forever.
Always remember that
I'll always support you.
Thank you for supporting me, brother.
I thought you'd never forgive me
for a moment.
Turgut Bey.
Your breed shall continue.
Eyvallah(thanks) brother.
Good luck, Turgut Bey.
Your tent shall cheer up,
your lives shall be long, my Bey.
Eyvallah(thanks) brother.
From now on, I entrust my sister
to you, Turgut Bey.
I am not going to be worried.
I appreciate that.
Eyvallah (thanks).
What am I going to do with these?
What are those, Cerkutay?
Millet.
You said Millets are necessary
for the wedding!
I found some!
Good, Cerkutay.
You are starting to gain my favor!
Did you just beat me or fondle me?
Come on Cerkutay.
Leave now.
What did Turgut Bey do?
He prepared a feast for his wedding!
What did he do for Mari Hatun?
He butchered stallion, sheep, and ram!
Did he break hearts?
He neither broke hearts nor uttered
bad words!
He married Mari Hatun!
May Allah make them happy!
Amin! You shall be happy!
You shall have a long marriage!
I wish my Boran was here.
My brother's voice is absent, my Bey.
My Bey.
I heard it from Aygül Hatun.
Boran is not well.
What happened to my valiant?
He is going pretty mad.
He is talking to himself.
My mountain-like valiant!
Boran!
Who did this to you?
How could they do this to you?
I can't accept it, Gündüz.
Put an end to this.
I heard something awful today.
Nikola tried to kill Mari.
Turgut Bey was there just in time.
We sent Mari to death with our hands,
Gündüz!
How are going to get rid of this sin?
What if she couldn't run away?
Hatuns keep saying they're going to
find the betrayer who abducted Mari.
May Allah hide our situation.
My Bey!
Are you okay?
I am fine.
Go inside, Ayse.
Hay Masha Allah(praise be) my valiants!
I knew you'd come!
I knew.
I told my Gonca to cook dinner!
She'll be here soon.
We'll eat and eat, my brothers!
If Cerkutay leaves us any food of course.
Come on, have a nice meal!
Bless your hands!
Boran,
My bey.
No.
We were having a meal, my bey...
...join us.
You said we were going to talk.
You kept your word.
Yes,...
...I kept my word.
Whose bey am I?
Praise be!
You're Boran's bey.
Kayı's bey.
You're Kayı's bey.
And you are the most valiant
alp of kayı.
You are my most loyal alp.
My bey,...
...I became Gündüz Bey's alp.
I owed allegiance to him.
Good for you!
We trusted you with the kayı's throne.
Whoever sits there, you'll stand by them.
But now that you came...
...I am your alp now right?
I'm going now.
But when I come back, you'll have my back.
Now, promise me that...
...you're going to get yourself together.
Boran, come to your senses.
I'm leaving now, when I come back...
...I want to see you standing strong,...
...fit as a fiddle.
Do you understand my brother?
Yes, my bey.
Brother.
Dear Allah,...
...give me strength to endure this test.
My Osman and now my father.
Help my Osman to overcome
his struggles my Allah.
Help him, dear Allah.
Amen.
Help him...
Bala
Osman!
Bala,...
...don't cry.
Don't cry.
Are you well?
We are well, thank Allah.
Don't worry...
...I'm well too.
Your wellbeing is more important.
We're well my Osman...
...we're well but we're going through
Allah's tough tests.
First you, now my father.
I know.
I know all about it.
There is one more thing I know about.
And that, we will see better days.
If Allah permits, my bey.
I also got some good news.
Mari and Turgut got
married in Harmankaya.
Is that so?
I would want to witness Mari's joy.
But it's fate, I guess it
has to be this way.
They are happy now.
Don't keep standing, sit down, my Osman.
No, Bala.
I'm going to speak to my brother.
No way my Osman, Vizier's soldiers
are patrolling around everywhere.
- Don't go.
- Bala,
Do not leave your tent.
Come on, sit.
Be careful.
Traitor,...
...traitor huh?
Traitor.
My brother?
Osman, what are you doing here?
Brother,...
...I trusted you...
...as my brother Gündüz Bey!
Osman, what are you doing?
Gündüz Bey who sits at the throne...
...and makes a deal with a traitor.
Whatever I've done was for
the welfare of our tribe.
Selling out our tribe is for its welfare?!
Being vizier's slave is for its welfare?!
Should we be beys like you Osman?
Should we set the tribe on fire, Osman?
Should we suffer the next pain without
the end of the previous one, Osman?
I saw you at Inegöl.
I saw you and did not tell anyone about it
I don't want any more pain, Osman!
You are making a mistake brother!
If so, you should have told them!
You should have said, "Osman is here"!
You should have stabbed me in the back!
When I saw you with them...
...at that moment you were done for me!
We do business!
We enrich our tribe!
We care for the welfare of our people!
Do you want an enemy?
You don't have a brother!
You disgraced our tribe!
I would have never trusted you
if I had known you would do that!
Osman.
Osman!
Everything you've done was a mistake.
Now, I'm making up for those mistakes.
Now, I'm healing those wounds!
You made a mistake, Osman.
Watch your mouth!
You are afraid of battle.
Only...
...the brave is not afraid of battle.
- Brother,
- Gündüz Bey!
I'm afraid...
...you will end up like my uncle.
My bey, say something!
My bey, we can't come in!
- My bey, are you alright?
- My bey, the door is stuck!
Gündüz Bey?
What is going on here?
That Vizier Alemshah,...
...without dealing with him...
...there is no rest for me.
He has made me so wrathful.
He will pay the biggest prize.
I feel you, Osman Bey.
I hate Nikola just as much as...
...you hate Vizier.
Do not worry at all. In the end, both
of us will get what we want.
Let's not wait any longer then.
Let's head to Bilecik.
Osman Bey,...
...I was afraid I could not catch up.
If Allah permits, you won't go
without me right Osman Bey?
No,...
...this time, I'm going without you.
You'll stay here.
Don't leave Mari on
your first day together.
Horses are with me too,
do not worry.
As you wish.
Let's give you a send-off then.
What is going on in here?
Where are ahis?
Why aren't tradesmen
opening up their shops?
As long as Edebalı is not released from
the dungeon, shops will not be opened.
You are rebelling...
...you can't do this, you
can't stop the trade.
Do you think we will trade after...
...you capture the Sheik.
You think you're so smart?
Sheik Edebalı might be in prison but,...
...I would not let anything happen to him.
Whoever harms him will have to face me.
Where was your mind when...
...you were capturing the Sheik.
Take care of yourself.
Are you for justice?
Or for unreasoning?
Vizier Alemshah!
Your dark dungeons cannot
dim the light of our Sheik!
Release our sheik!
Urfan Orhan
Praise be my valiant!
Look at your grandmother.
Praise be!
You smell very nice!
Go to your mother.
May I come in?
- Bala,
- You may come in.
Welcome, Bala.
Come, my girl.
Happy to be here!
Bala, my beautiful girl,
you seem very well.
Zehra has been taking
care of you very well.
Yes, bless her.
She helped me a lot.
- Mother,
- Yes.
I got some good news for you.
What is it, my girl?
Osman came last night.
My dear Osman came?
Osman did come.
Allah protected him, he did not
get captured by Vizier's soldiers.
Thank Allah!
So, tell me...
...is my valiant well?
He is well mother, don't worry.
Vizier your excellence, I got something
very important I want to talk to you about
Go ahead, Gündüz Bey.
I've heard what happened, Osman
had apparently broken into your place.
That is not the issue.
The issue is...
...what is Sheik Edebalı
doing at the dungeon?
Edebalı set us up by colluding with Osman.
And now serving his sentence
for betraying the government.
People make mistakes, Vizier Alemshah.
If he is an occupant, he should
have a chance to redeem himself.
Can't you see what's going on?
People are revolting.
If the son of Ertuğrul Ghazi, Gündüz
Bey wants something from me...
...I will not turn it down.
Thank you, Vizier Alemshah.
It will not happen again,
I vouch for my Sheik.
Our wish is to gain
the trust of the people.
If people are angry at us for Edebalı...
...it means that we have made a mistake.
Celali, release Sheik Edebalı immediately.
As you wish, Vizier your exellence.
I'll release Edebalı but,...
...I want you to deliver
him to his people...
...that way Edebalı's trust
towards you will increase.
I'm heading to Bilecik
for Bazaar, right now.
And you, after delivering the Sheik to
the people, come to Bilecik Gündüz Bey.
Allah bless you Vizier Alemshah.
Alps!
We will wait for Vizier at Bilecik Castle
My bey, what will we do with
Vizier after we capture him?
He made me so wrathful that...
...I want to rip his lying tongue out...
...and burn it.
For the things, he did to the sheik,
I want to gauge his ugly eyes out...
...and separate his head
from his filthy body.
I will feed him to jackals so that his
blood does not pollute the ground.
Allah bless you, my bey!
But how are we going to
get to the Bilecik Castle?
We will get there without even
drawing out our weapons Göktuğ.
We will be waiting for
the Vizier, inside.
He deserves such a greeting.
Alps!
Let' go, let's go!
BILECIK CASTLE
Even the Lord is serving his soldiers
under my Bey's command.
We mean to destroy the tyrant brother,...
...let no one stand against us.
Alps!
To the rooms, to the corridor, disperse
around all sides of the castle.
I'm going to Vizier Alemshas's room.
He will be acquainted with
my weapon of justice.
As you command my bey!
Come on!
Vizier.
This bazaar will make us a lot of dough.
It doesn't matter where it is.
As Osman is living as a fugitive,
we will become richer.
To be honest, I did not expect Vizier
to be able to achieve all of this.
The order he brought benefited us the most
The goods are coming tonight right?
Of course.
They'll be on the stall by
the morning light.
There will be a great festival
tomorrow at Bilecik.
Let's have the Vizier join us.
Sir, Vizier Alemshah is coming.
The Vizier of Seljuq State
Vizier Alam Shah.
Here is the architect of our system.
We created this system together, Lords.
We are going to
move together to make it work.
Absolutely, Vizier Alam Shah.
This market will contribute a lot to
our economy, thanks to you.
From east to west, from north to south...
...Richness will fly into our castles.
Once we initiate the market tomorrow...
...we'll see everything about richness,
Kosses.
Vizier.
You are going to get what you deserve.
My Bey will make him pay.
He'll regret his cruelty.
His bones will crack!
May Allah prevent any misfortune.
My Bey shall settle things at once.
Vizier has a lot to answer.
His end shouldn't be quick, Saltuk.
You have been...
...covered with the blood of
many cruels...
...you have been...
...a nightmare for many betrayers.
However...
...however, this one is different.
May the Creator send us brave enemies.
This one is two-faced!
It is my duty to...
...cut him into two pieces.
Watch out.
Your eyes are about to be charmed by the
swords that I will exhibit in the market.
The protector of our system, Gündüz Bey.
Welcome.
Thank you Vizier Alam-Shah.
Yes, now that Gündüz Bey is here,
we can let ourselves into our rooms.
We must rest for the market's
opening tomorrow.
You are right, Rogatus, we should rest
so that...
...we can wake up fresh.
Here.
Every cruel...
...needs an Osman!
Come to me, Vizier.
Come to your end.
Vizier!
Gündüz Bey, this is your room.
Good night.
This is yours, Vizier.
One of the biggest rooms.
We will be here, Hadrat Vizier.
What's that?
You are taking deep breaths.
Did you just realise these
are your last breaths?
No soldiers...
...and no slaves that you step on...
...are available here.
What are you going to do?
Vizier?
Osman Bey.
I see that my power influenced you.
You set up a trick to...
...catch me alone.
Trick?
You know about tricks better, Vizier.
You know about that better!
However...
I ruin tricks.
I ruin plans.
What is the source of your courage, Osman?
You have no tribe.
You have no soldiers.
You have no power.
There is no people who would obey you.
I have faith in my chest...
...filling me like a breath!
I have a belief that the Creator stands
with the good!
What about you?
You lack it.
This is why you are afraid.
This is why you are looking at the door.
It is not your dare to question...
...the courage and faith of the
Vizier of Seljuq State.
Questioning?
I am going to judge you with my sword.
Osman.
Your words exceed your power.
You may regret tomorrow.
Let me think about tomorrow.
You are not going to have
a tomorrow, Alam-Shah!
You...
...betrayed Turks' case!
You clouded the future of Turks!
You burned that platanus which we
have been watering...
...with our blood!
Now...
Now I am going to burn you too.
Now I am going to...
...hang you
on the branches of mighty platanus.
I shall not be called Osman...
...if I don't do what I say.
My sword,
covered with the blood of cruels, ...
...is going to remove you...
...from your false way.
Hadrat Vizier!
Alam Shah.
Vizier, are you okay?
Vizier?
When the cruels are being cruel...
...we bring the sword of justice!
Vizier!
Please contact us for any inquiries
turkision@gmail.com